hi spring fans in this installment of
嗨，春季粉丝在本期中
spring tips we're gonna look at the
Spring 的技巧，我们要看看
spring shell project now I don't blame
我现在不怪Spring Shell项目
it you if you haven't heard of it yet
如果你还没有听说的话
alright this is a fairly sort of under
好吧，这是一个相当
the radar project tender and that's
雷达项目招标，那就是
because largely the biggest consumer is
因为很大程度上最大的消费者是
other projects right the spring shell
其他项目对Spring Shell
codebase originated in spring roo a
源于spring roo a的代码库
project that we originated more than ten
我们发起了十多个项目
years ago and there it served our CLI
年前，它在那里为我们的CLI服务
use case right we had them build a
用例权，我们让他们建立了一个
client a command-line client that you
客户端您所使用的命令行客户端
could use and it was interactive and
可以使用，它是交互式的，
that command line was the tool with
该命令行是
which you interacted with the framework
您与框架进行了互动
with the runtime we took that source
在运行时，我们采用了该源
source code and it's sort of survived
源代码，它还可以生存
it's a it's been used in other projects
这是一个已经在其他项目中使用的
but most notably it was polished often
但最值得注意的是它经常抛光
and we worked a little bit to support
我们做了一些努力来支持
our use cases for spring XD which of
我们的Spring XD用例
course is now spring cloud dataflow the
当然现在是 Spring Cloud 数据流了
original source code is based on J line
原始源代码基于J线
so the the basic you know console read
因此，您知道的基本控制台
line support all that kind of stuff all
线支持所有这些东西
that's supported by J line and spring
由J线和Spring 支持
shell has been sort of an abstraction on
shell有点像
top of that now it's just reached a new
最重要的是，它刚刚达到一个新的
milestone it's a to that om2 right so
具有里程碑意义的是om2，所以
there's a new release a new version of
有一个新版本的新版本
it that looks very promising and one of
它看起来非常有前途，其中之一
the biggest features of this new release
此新版本的最大功能
is that it's based on spring boots so
是基于 spring boot 的
there's a whole Auto configuration
有一个完整的自动配置
mechanism and a framework and ton so
机制和框架等等
let's we're gonna look at that and I'm
让我们来看一下，我
under no illusions or you know delusions
没有幻想，或者你知道错觉
rather of the the market for for people
而不是人的市场
building shell based applications I'm
建立基于外壳的应用程序
not saying this is gonna be the next big
不是说这将是下一个大
thing that you should all run out and do
你们都应该用光并做的事情
but if you have a some sort of back-end
但是如果您有某种后端
use case or some sort of tooling that
用例或某种工具
needs to be built operations tool or
需要构建操作工具或
just certain sort of dashboard ex-marine
只是某种仪表板而已
sure whatever there might be use case
确保可能存在用例
for it to be generated and to be
为了它的产生和成为
supported with the shell right a shell
用外壳支撑着一个外壳
based a user interface as opposed to
基于用户界面而不是
maybe a more full-featured web
也许功能更全的网站
application which would take
需要的申请
considerably longer to develop and you
发展相当长的时间
know maybe you just want something with
知道也许你只是想要
that you can use to administer batch
您可以用来管理批处理
jobs for example or you want something
例如工作，或者您想要一些东西
you can use to
你可以用来
to interact with your with your back-end
与您的后端互动
REST API to pull up data whatever your
REST API可以提取任何数据
use cases moment you know you can very
用例时刻，您知道您可以
very quickly get a working prototype
很快得到一个可以工作的原型
with a shell whereas it would take a
与外壳，而这需要一个
considerably considerably more time to
相当多的时间
to get the same experience to get the
获得相同的体验
same sort of interacting interactivity
同一种互动互动
with a web application and you know this
与网络应用程序，你知道这一点
is not for everybody
不适合所有人
one thing to keep in mind is that this
要记住的一件事是
is a shell right so this is gonna be
是贝壳，所以这将是
it's gonna just take advantage of
它只会利用
features that work more readily on UNIX
在UNIX上更容易使用的功能
or UNIX flavored operating systems that
或UNIX风格的操作系统
said you should still work on Windows
说你仍然应该在Windows上工作
and we know of course it works on
我们当然知道它可以
Windows with cygwin and and and other
Windows与cygwin和and等
you know UNIX flavored um modes on top
您知道UNIX风格的um模式
of Windows alright so we don't build a
Windows的功能，所以我们不构建
new a CRM it'll it'll be an application
新的CRM，它将成为一个应用程序
that you can use to talk to a CRM which
您可以用来与CRM对话的
of course I don't have a serum is just
我当然没有血清
an app that you can use to manage
您可以用来管理的应用
customer data and it's just a very
客户数据，这只是一个非常
boring domains I figured we go with that
我认为我们会选择无聊的领域
so let's call this the CRM shell and
所以我们称其为CRM Shell
we're gonna use the Lombok support and
我们将使用龙目岛支持，
spring boot and when you spin good spin
spring boot ，当你旋转时旋转得很好
boot - and five now there is no shell
引导-现在有五个没有外壳
checkbox
复选框
at least not yet anyway which is a bit
至少还没有，这有点
of a bummer and I hope to see that
简直让人不知所措，我希望看到
change but the reason we're choosing to
变化，但我们选择的原因
that om5 is because we want the
那个om5是因为我们想要
milestone and you know snapshot
里程碑，你知道快照
repositories editor arm even built right
仓库编辑器臂甚至正确建立
so by choosing m5 we already get that
所以通过选择m5我们已经得到了
for free as opposed to relying on the
是免费的，而不是依靠
assumption that we're gonna we can talk
假设我们会说话
to the maven central repository alright
到Maven中央存储库
so let's open up our build and we'll add
因此，让我们打开构建，然后添加
spring she'll start there so spring show
Spring ，她将从那里开始，所以春季秀
start or maybe it's ok or spring
开始，也许没事或 Spring
framework and it's not cloud but she'll
框架，而不是云，但她会
the version is to 1000 dot m2 let's see
版本是1000点m2
if that works good alright so our new
如果可以的话，那么我们的新产品
CRM shell is going to manage as I say
我说过，CRM Shell将进行管理
data from a CRM so we don't have a an
CRM中的数据，因此我们没有
tootie of type person that'll be
那种类型的人会
something that will manage that one
可以管理那个人的东西
we're not gonna actually use I don't
我们不会真正使用我不
have a REST API I don't have an actual
有一个REST API，我没有实际的
persistence to hear anything like that I
坚持听到我这样的话
have no sophisticated code we're just
没有复杂的代码，我们只是
gonna create a mock API a trivial API so
要创建一个简单的模拟API，所以
mad something with words to work so it's
用词疯狂地工作，所以它是
gonna support data of type person whose
将支持其类型的人的数据
get with a long ID and a name alright
带有长ID和好名字
there's that we want to be able to work
那就是我们希望能够工作
with that data so we'll locate a person
有了这些数据，我们就可以找到一个人
service and the service will be a it'll
服务，服务将是一个
support I don't know what is it going to
支持我不知道会发生什么
support it'll supported a number of
支持它将支持许多
different use cases it'll support asking
支持的不同用例
is a user connected alright so we'll say
是用户连接好吗，所以我们说
something for now I'll just return false
现在我会返回false
it'll support connecting alright so
它会支持连接好吧，所以
avoid connect string user string PW
避免连接字符串用户字符串PW
it'll support disconnecting so I'll get
它支持断开连接，所以我会得到
back to that it'll support returning a
回到它会支持返回一个
person by its ID all right so there's
凭身份证的人没事，所以
that what else do we need we want to
我们还需要什么
find all people by name so string name
通过名称查找所有人，因此找到字符串名称
right
对
good so that's our surface area API
很好，那就是我们的表面积API
naturally we need they know there is a
自然，我们需要他们知道有一个
little matter of data we need actual
实际需要的数据很少
data in order for this to work so let's
数据以使其正常工作，所以让我们
go ahead and write some data when this
继续写一些数据
beam gets initialized we'll go ahead and
梁被初始化，我们将继续
write some data to the database and our
将一些数据写入数据库，我们的
database in this case I'm using giant
在这种情况下，我使用的是巨型数据库
you know sarcastic air quotes here is a
你知道讽刺的空气报价是
local map a map of people ID to to the
将人的ID本地地图映射到
person record itself and of course it's
人记录自己，当然是
in memory but it's still just a map okay
在内存中，但仍然只是一张地图还可以
so this dot people will touch put all
所以这个点的人会触摸把所有
and we have to put in a map of data so
我们必须放入数据图
we'll say streamed of I'm gonna get some
我们会说流媒体我会得到一些
sample data right some sample dated with
样本数据对一些带有日期的样本
some similar names so Stefan Stefan
一些类似的名字，所以斯特凡斯特凡
James what else do we want so there's a
詹姆斯，我们还想要什么，所以有一个
number of names and we're gonna map the
名称的数量，我们将映射
name to a new person entity so there's
命名为新的人物实体，因此
that and of course in order to capture
那当然是为了捕捉
an ID we need to generate it somehow
我们需要以某种方式生成它的ID
I'll just use an atomic long to generate
我将使用原子长生成
it and we'll say IDs dot increment and
它，我们会说ID点增量和
gets and we'll pass them the name
得到，我们将名称传递给他们
attribute here and then we've got the
属性在这里，然后我们得到了
name so now we want to collect all of it
命名，所以现在我们要收集所有
into a map and then add that to our our
进入地图，然后将其添加到我们的
existing map and in order to do that I
现有的地图，为了做到这一点，我
need to provide a to buy functions the
需要提供购买功能
first function is gonna say given a
第一个功能是说给定一个
person give me a key which I'll do by
人给我一把钥匙，我该怎么做
returning the ID and the second will say
返回ID，第二个会说
just give me a value of course that's
给我一个价值当然是
the P itself and we'll store all of that
P本身，我们将存储所有这些
into a database let's see we got here
进入数据库，让我们看看我们到了这里
Oh wrong way around okay and person map
哦，错误的路线可以和人贴图
will store that and that's this right
将存储它，就是这样
leg that's where it all goes it is in
腿就是一切的所在
that map alright so there's our sample
那张地图好，所以有我们的样本
data when application get started let's
应用程序启动时的数据
go ahead and implement this code so
继续执行此代码，以便
we'll have some data private final
我们会有一些私人决赛
atomic sorry yeah atomic bullion
是的，对不起，原子的金条
connected equals no atomic bullion great
连接不等于没有原子金
and I'll say this dot connected that get
我会说这个点连接起来
great this start connected that set is
很棒的开始连接那集是
equal to true this dot connected that
等于true这个点连接了那个
set is equal to false when I say this
我说这个的时候set等于false
dot people don't get ID and finally this
点人们没有身份证，最后这
dot people dot values dot stream dot
点人们点值点流点
filter P P that get name that contains
过滤包含名称的PP
name alright so there's that to
好的名字，就是这样
lowercase to a little of case collecting
小写到少量案例收集
it all into a list and there we go
全部放入列表，然后我们去
there's our basic endpoints okay not a
有我们的基本终点，不是
very fancy domain I don't really care
非常花哨的域名，我不在乎
about the domain it's when I have some
关于域名，当我有一些
stuff that we can use for our simple
我们可以用来简单的东西
example we've got a service now we've
例如我们现在有服务
got that let's build a shell right let's
知道了，让我们建立一个外壳吧
build a shell by which we can interact
建立一个我们可以互动的外壳
with that database so we're gonna have a
与那个数据库，所以我们将有一个
class for a our first set of operations
我们的第一套操作课
our first set of commands supporting
我们的第一组命令支持
connectivity right so we'll call this
正确的连接性，所以我们称之为
connection commands and in order for
连接命令和顺序
this to do its work when I inject that
当我注入它来完成它的工作时
person's service or we can just call us
人的服务，或者我们可以给我们打电话
the CRM service right invariably
CRM服务权利无一例外
yeah all that'll work so I'm gonna
是的，所有这些都会起作用，所以我要
inject the CRM service here anyway
无论如何在这里注入CRM服务
aren't then don't make this a shell
那就不要把它变成外壳
component and we'll inject that into the
组件，然后将其注入
constructor and we use that to create
构造函数，我们用它来创建
our first command so let's create a
我们的第一个命令，所以让我们创建一个
command here
在这里命令
Connect right and that'll take two
正确连接，需要两个
parameters the username and the password
参数用户名和密码
and I'm going to call this the would
我将其称为
give it a string so connect to the CRM
给它一个字符串，以便连接到CRM
this is a description of what we're
这是对我们的描述
gonna do here and of course in our case
要在这里做，当然就我们而言
we're just gonna connect forwarding the
我们只是要连接转发
username and the password now I can
现在可以输入用户名和密码了
imagine wanting to report back to the
想像一下要向
client what's happened I don't wanna
客户端发生了什么我不想
talk to the client so this let's see
与客户交谈，让我们看看
what happens here first let's run this
首先在这里发生什么，让我们运行这个
and we'll say CD
我们会说CD
equals true clean install and I will do
等于真正的全新安装，我会做
that
那
Java - jar target's CEO Nichelle
Java-Jar Target的首席执行官Nichelle
all right you can see at the top there
好吧，你可以在顶部看到
we've got a little prompt we can say
我们有一点提示可以说
okay show me the commands to help it
好吧，告诉我一些帮助的命令
shows me all the built-in commands
向我展示了所有内置命令
including the one to declare the console
包括一个声明控制台的
to exit exit go crate or control C and D
退出退出板条箱或控制C和D
help will show you all the commands so
帮助将向您显示所有命令，因此
that's what I've just invoked to get
这就是我刚刚为了得到
this listing here script it actually
此清单实际上是脚本
takes a file and it'll allow me to
需要一个文件，它将允许我
provide any commands I could provide in
提供我可以提供的任何命令
the shell I can provide them in a file
我可以在文件中提供它们的外壳
and script them right I can automate it
并正确编写脚本，我可以使其自动化
and of course our one custom Connect
当然还有我们的一个自定义连接
command so let's see what that looks
命令，让我们看一下看起来
like
喜欢
Connect equals username J password is P
连接等于用户名J密码为P
there we go so we have no you know it
我们去了那里所以我们没有你知道
worked nothing is wrong but it didn't
没事没错，但没错
you know as far as I'm concerned we
就我而言，你知道我们
don't know what just happened right we
不知道发生了什么事吧
don't have any feedback so let's report
没有任何反馈，让我们报告
back to the client what's just happened
回到客户那里发生了什么
but when we do that I want to make sure
但是当我们这样做时，我想确保
that we get the recipe for reporting
我们得到了报告的配方
back to the client done right one time
回到客户正确的一次
and then reuse that recipe right so
然后重新使用该配方，这样
instead of you know reinventing go and
而不是你知道重塑去和
log it with abstraction I think we're
我以抽象的方式记录它
just gonna create a little a little
会创造一些
service that manages the console output
管理控制台输出的服务
because again that's an actual that's a
因为这又是实际的
competency of this application is we're
这个应用程序的能力是我们
actually talking to the client you know
与你认识的客户交谈
on the console this is not just about
在控制台上，这不只是关于
blogging so console service and all
博客，所以控制台服务和所有
we're gonna do is manage the
我们要做的是管理
interactions to system out basically so
与系统的交互基本上是这样的
ok and point here public void right
好吧，指向这里公共无效的权利
string message and it's going to take a
字符串消息，它将需要一个
an array of arguments if there are
参数数组（如果有）
available and I will say this dot out
可用，我会说出这个点
dot print this okay and this dot out dot
点打印好了，这个点出来
print F message and orgs in order to
打印F消息和组织以
pass that in we'll have to cast it to an
通过它，我们必须将其转换为
array and they'll say this that out dot
阵列，他们会说出那个点
print line very good so there's our our
打印线非常好，所以我们的
basic console output I like a little
基本的控制台输出，我有点喜欢
color and I help em application so I'll
颜色，我帮助他们申请，所以我会
grab the color codes yeah the ANSI color
抓取颜色代码，是ANSI颜色
codes here and
这里的代码和
use those two two spicing up our output
用这两个两个加倍我们的输出
here a little bit okay so private final
这里有点好，所以私人决赛
string and see reset Nancy yellow so
字符串，请参阅重置南希黄色
we're gonna say first just stood out the
我们要说的是首先脱颖而出
print line or not rather to print and
打印行还是不打印
see yellow okay and that'll be the ante
看到黄色没事，那将是事前
reset and see reset very good so now
重置，看到重置非常好，所以现在
let's rewrite that or rework this code
让我们重写一下或重新编写这段代码
here to reflect the fact that we have
在这里反映出我们拥有的事实
done what we expected to do private
完成了我们期望做的私人工作
final console service console and well
最终控制台服务控制台以及
inject that into the constructor and
注入到构造函数中
we'll report it here so this dot console
我们将在此处报告，以便此点控制台
dot right connected username all right
点右连接用户名可以
not bad let's see what that happened
不错，让我们看看发生了什么
does for us so here we go alright so if
为我们做的，所以我们在这里走了，所以如果
we go here connect it says connected J
我们去这里连接它说连接J
and it's in yellow right so I used the
它是黄色的，所以我用了
ANSI color code there to signal that the
那里的ANSI颜色代码表示
following text should be in color and
以下文字应为彩色，
then when I hit the reset it goes back
然后当我点击重置时，它会返回
to whatever color was there before all
不管有什么颜色
right so that works that seems to be
对的，这样的作品似乎是
working let's go ahead and implement our
让我们继续实施我们的工作
disconnect functionality here and this
在此断开功能
is fairly straightforward right we just
是非常简单的权利，我们只是
say public void disconnect and I will
说公共无效断开连接，我会
say this dot cor m dot disconnect all
说这个点Cor m点断开所有
right the problem as you can imagine is
可以想象的问题是
that these things should not be run at
这些东西不应该在
the same time right so I've got two
在同一时间，所以我有两个
different commands here but I want to
这里有不同的命令，但我想
give some sort of feedback to the client
给客户一些反馈
that when I'm connected
当我连接时
I can disconnect but when I'm not
我可以断开连接，但是当我不连接时
connected I shouldn't be able to
连接我不应该
disconnect because well that's
断开连接，因为那是
nonsensical right as similarly if I'm
无理的权利，如果我是
already connected I shouldn't be able to
已经连接，我不应该
connect it again right so we need to
重新连接正确，所以我们需要
give some sort of visual feedback so I'm
提供某种视觉反馈，所以我
going to do that is to create a
要做的就是创建一个
availability object
可用性对象
return back to the client when asked
询问时返回客户
write the the framework will give us an
写框架会给我们一个
opportunity we can signal to the client
我们可以向客户发出信号的机会
which one you should use
您应该使用哪一个
by creating an or by annotating a method
通过创建一个或通过注释方法
with shell method availability and then
使用shell方法的可用性，然后
returning an availability object and
返回可用性对象，并
this availability object will be used by
此可用性对象将由
all commands in this the shell component
shell组件中的所有命令
to determine whether they should be
确定是否应该
grayed out or not whether there should
是否变灰
be activated or not this is not what we
是否被激活，这不是我们所需要的
want that's interesting because it gives
希望这很有趣，因为它给
you a single way to provide feedback
您提供反馈的一种方法
what I want is to have a different
我想要的是与众不同
availability for this then I do for this
为此的可用性，然后我为此
obviously one that has to be exclusive
显然，这必须是排他的
to the other so there's another
彼此之间，所以还有另一个
convenient mechanism here we can just
方便的机制在这里我们可以
say availability disconnect and then
说可用性断开，然后
suffix it with the name availability and
后缀名称为available，并且
our job is to say ok disconnect is only
我们的工作是说好断开只是
available when we're connected so this
当我们连接时可用
step serum that is connected good
连接好的步血清
availability is available otherwise yeah
可用性可用，否则
you know you're not connected okay so
你知道你没有连接好吗
that's charity straightforward
慈善直接
that'll be called by convention when
按照惯例，
looking at the availability for that
寻找可用性
method similarly we can do the same
方法类似，我们可以做同样的事情
thing here for the connect command
这里的连接命令
and the the roll was released right a
然后该卷就被释放了
reverse rather so we're gonna say if
相反，所以我们要说
we're not connected then this is
我们没有连接，那么这是
available otherwise we're gonna say
可用，否则我们会说
you're already connected all right let's
您已经连接好了，让我们
clean that up and we'll start that again
清理一下，我们将再次开始
all right
好吧
so actually before I get too ahead of
所以实际上在我超前之前
myself
我
help shows that we cannot disconnect but
帮助表明我们无法断开连接，但是
we can connect good username a password
我们可以连接好用户名和密码
P whatever good help again shows me that
P任何好的帮助再次向我表明
now disconnect is visible right but I
现在断开连接可见，但是我
cannot connect the asterisks signals
无法连接星号信号
that it's currently unavailable right
目前无法使用
okay so that works but in order for me
好吧，那行得通，但为了我
to get that feedback I have to use the
为了获得反馈，我必须使用
help command each time to see the
每次查看帮助命令
asterisks next to the command what I'd
命令旁边的星号
like to do is instead to have that
我喜欢做的是
information visible in the prompt so
提示中显示的信息如此
we're going to do that when a critic
当批评家的时候我们要做
custom prompt provider so connected
自定义提示提供程序已连接
prompt provider implement prompt
提示提供者实施提示
provider prompt providers a callback
提供程序提示提供程序回调
method a callback interface in the
方法中的回调接口
spring shell project and the job is very
Spring Shell项目，工作非常
simple when asked we turn this a prompt
简单，当被问到时，我们将其提示
that'll get shown in lieu of shell : you
它将代替shell显示：您
know greater then right so we're gonna
知道更多然后正确，所以我们要
say private final CRM service CRM I had
说我拥有私人最终CRM服务CRM
a constructor argument and we'll say
构造函数参数，我们将说
string message equals spring CRM will
字符串消息等于Spring CRM will
have a little value there will say a
有一点价值，会说
string format okay and the in the output
字符串格式还可以，然后在输出中
here we're gonna say this dot serum that
在这里，我们要说这点血清
is connected connected
已连接
otherwise disconnected okay damn okay to
否则断开连接好该死好吧
space so there we go now we just return
空间，所以我们现在就去，我们只是返回
an attributed string it can be a lot
属性字符串可能很多
more things if you want it to be but for
如果想要的话还有更多的事情，但是
our purposes it's just gonna be a string
我们的目的只是字符串
right so that's that's easy enough let's
对，那就很简单，让我们
go ahead and restart let's see what
继续并重新启动，让我们看看
happens there look at that it's a spring
碰巧那里是 Spring
serum disconnected alright and if we
血清断开连接好吗，如果我们
connect yeah it says connected J and it
连接是的，它说连接了J，并且它
says connected down there so we've got
说连接到那里，所以我们有
much more visible much more useful
更可见更有用
feedback there I think that's kind of
那里的反馈，我认为这是
convenient and of course you can use a
方便，当然您可以使用
scared you know entity cutters and all
害怕你知道实体切割机和所有
that stuff all apply there as well okay
这些东西都适用于那里
so we've got that and to build a new
所以我们已经有了并建立一个新的
command let's build something that
命令让我们建立一些
allows us to talk to that repository of
让我们可以与
data the the people records the persons
数据人记录人
so we'll create a new command grouping
所以我们将创建一个新的命令分组
here I'll say class people comment all
在这里我会说全班同学都评论
right so this allow us to work with the
对，所以这使我们可以与
directory and this is just a shell
目录，这只是一个外壳
component and we have an endpoint here
组件，我们在这里有一个端点
that returns it's gonna be a directory
返回它将会是一个目录
endpoint and it'll do something with
端点，它将与
records of type person so there's this
类型人的记录所以有这个
shell method directory interact with the
shell方法目录与
directory alright so there's our
目录好，所以有我们的
convenient command and we're gonna
方便的命令，我们将
basically edit what we're gonna find a
基本上编辑我们将要找到的
person and then edit it right but the
人，然后对其进行正确的编辑，但
problem is that spring shell doesn't
问题是Spring Shell没有
know about a person right our person is
知道一个人对，我们这个人是
a an entity it's a domain model it's a
一个实体，它是一个领域模型，它是一个
detail it's it's a number of things but
细节是很多事情，但是
it is not a spring shell type so we need
它不是Spring Shell类型，所以我们需要
to we need to teach it how to do that
我们需要教它怎么做
and when here we can just use the the
当我们在这里可以使用
convertor framework the substrate in
转换器框架中的基板
spring that it's been there since I
Spring ，自从我就去过那里
don't know three dotto it's been around
不知道有3个dotto
forever it's a a mechanism that we use
永远是我们使用的一种机制
to deaf strings into your business
充耳不闻
domain and visa-versa
域和反之亦然
and it's used all over the frameworks
它已在所有框架中使用
all of the ecosystem all over all of us
我们所有人的整个生态系统
Pingdom so if you don't form binding in
Pingdom，所以如果您不形成绑定
the spring MVC or web flex
Spring MVC或Web Flex
you're using that if using spring
如果使用Spring ，就使用它
innovation or if you're doing certain
创新或您是否正在做某些事情
spring expression language constructs if
Spring Expression Language 构造if
you're doing you know just just any
你在做你知道什么
number of things right anyway anywhere
随处可见的事物数量
you can think of it there's probably a
你可以想到的是
some sort of converter conversion
某种转换器转换
service mechanism in there somewhere so
服务机制在那里某处
we're gonna create a custom converter
我们将创建一个自定义转换器
which is gonna be plugged into the
这将被插入
conversion service which is as I say a
正如我所说的，转换服务
part of spring for at least a decade I
Spring 的至少十年我
guess almost a decade so I'm gonna say
我猜大概十年了，我要说
class person converter implements
类人转换器
converter of type string two type person
类型字符串二类人的转换器
and the contract is fairly simple it
合同很简单
says given a source convert the record
说给定来源转换记录
so what we're going to do is we're going
所以我们要做的是
to assume that the the string that's
假设该字符串是
gonna be entered is uniform because we
要输入的是统一的，因为我们
can parse uniform right so that's I've
可以解析统一的权利，这就是我
got a regular expression that I've
我有一个正则表达式
conjured up here and we'll use that to
想到这里，我们将用它来
make short work of parsing this the
缩短解析时间
schema that I've dreamt up okay so
我梦dream以求的架构，所以
private final there we are so a regular
私人决赛，我们是如此常规
expression pattern and what that's gonna
表达模式，那会是什么
look for is records of the following
寻找以下记录
form like this you know fubar right so
这样的形式，你知道fubar吧
it's gonna keep only 42 this is it's
它只会保留42个，这是
gonna have a group called that'll
会有一个叫做
support that number there right okay so
支持那个号码好吧，所以
we want to use that when I say okay this
我想说这个的时候我们想用那个
dot pattern dot match your source and
点图案点匹配您的来源，
map to a matcher if match or dot find
如果找到匹配项或点，则映射到匹配器
then we say match or dot loop and we
然后说匹配或点循环，我们
don't want the whole expression we just
不想整个表达，我们只是
want that one group that matches the you
想要与您匹配的那一组
know the inner parentheses okay so
知道内在括号就可以了
that's the first group and we want to
那是第一组，我们想
say if string utils has text group
说字符串utils是否具有文本组
then long-dead parse long loop and I
然后长死解析长循环，我
will say long id equals and we'll look
会说长id等于，我们会看
at the patent this year on a service
在今年获得专利服务
here so we don't have the CM service
在这里，所以我们没有CM服务
here it just yet so let's do that
就在这里，让我们开始吧
private final CRM service okay I had a
私人最终CRM服务，好吧，我有一个
constructor argument there we'll say
构造函数参数，我们会说
this does serum dot find my ID right
这会使血清点正确找到我的ID吗
that's exactly what we're trying to do
这正是我们想要做的
after all
毕竟
otherwise we turn it on all right so
否则我们就把它打开
that's a fairly straightforward
那是相当简单的
implementation let's go ahead and try
实现让我们继续尝试
that out now don't know the fact that
那个现在不知道事实
we're expecting sort of a schema fide
我们期待某种模式的坚定
well-known text disturb you right for
知名文字会打扰您
now we're just trying to prove that this
现在我们只是试图证明
will work but as we'll see it's possible
会起作用，但正如我们将看到的那样
to get that auto filled for us so let's
为我们装满汽车，让我们
see directory person all right so we
看到目录的人好吧，所以我们
know that if it's of the form to
知道如果是这样的形式
whatever that will work right so do we
不管什么都行，我们也一样
we didn't do anything with it we have to
我们没有做任何事情，我们必须
give us the console service console and
给我们控制台服务控制台，
I'll say this dot console dot right
我会说这个dot console dot right
working with
与...合作
person that get name okay there's our
知道名字的人有我们的
rewritten code here we go
我们去重写代码
now right directory person to fool
现在对目录人愚弄
there we go so they're the the regular
我们去那里，所以他们是常客
expression is working right it says if I
表达正确，它说如果我
have that schema it doesn't matter what
有那个模式没关系
- after the parentheses can be a number
-括号后可以是数字
of characters space whatever as long as
字符空间，只要
that's true it'll be able to extract the
没错，它将能够提取
ID find the record and then print out
ID找到记录，然后打印出来
that working with Brian Brian do so and
与Brian Brian合作的过程
now of course this is all very well and
现在当然一切都很好
good but how often are our users gonna
很好，但是我们的用户多久一次
know that schema or want to remember it
知道那个模式或想记住它
first of all and then second of all
首先，然后是第二
they're not gonna know you know which ID
他们不会知道你知道哪个ID
corresponds to which user so this is
对应于哪个用户，所以这是
really painful we'd like to let them
真的很痛苦，我们想让他们
search so what I'm going to do is we're
搜索，所以我要做的是
going to provide a way for them to get
将为他们提供一种获取途径
auto completion as they type and as the
自动完成，因为他们键入和
typing tab they'll they'll get feedback
键入标签，他们将获得反馈
from the system telling them about
从系统告诉他们
records that could match their search ok
可以匹配搜索的记录
so here I'm going to provide a value
所以在这里我要提供一个价值
provider so class person value provider
提供者，因此，班级人员提供者
implements value provider and the job is
实现价值提供者，工作是
very simple it's a component and spring
非常简单，这是一个组成部分和Spring
shell and needs to know about that for
外壳，并需要了解有关
our argument here so the argument is a
我们在这里的论据是
shell option I'm going to tell it about
外壳选项，我将介绍一下
it using the class literal syntax there
它在那里使用类文字语法
so we're saying run this value provider
所以我们说经营这个价值提供者
when they're inspecting values of this
当他们检查此值时
type and the value provider that we're
类型和我们所提供的价值提供者
gonna write has a very simple job
要写有一个非常简单的工作
it says when something comes in and the
它说什么时候进来，
parameter get prime know type is a sign
参数获取素数知道类型是一个符号
up fold sign of all from the person keep
从人保持的所有折叠迹象
it and then you know returns record so
它，然后你知道返回记录，所以
private final CRM service CRM had a
私人最终CRM服务CRM拥有一个
constructor argument
构造函数参数
move that up there alright so let's see
好好把它移到那里，让我们看看
we're gonna say string current input
我们要说的是字符串当前输入
equals completion context current word
等于完成上下文当前单词
up to cursor and we're gonna say this
直到光标，我们要说这个
dot serum dot find by name looking for
点血清点按名称查找
the current input then we're going to
当前输入，然后我们将
stream it and then we're gonna turn it
流式传输，然后我们将其旋转
into a collection of completion proposal
纳入完成建议书中
so we got a map at first so P string
所以我们首先得到了一个地图，所以P字符串
that format like this like that all
像这样的格式
right
对
so it'll be P get ID P that get name
所以它将是P获得ID P获得名称
that come that map completion proposal
那个地图完成建议
new that collect so that's our rewritten
新的，所以我们重写了
code and all we're doing is we're saying
代码，我们要做的就是说
find all the records that match the
查找与该记录匹配的所有记录
current string that's been input that's
当前输入的字符串是
this bit right here take it and create
这一点就在这里拿来创造
it we don't encode it in that schema
我们没有在那个模式中对它进行编码
that we talked about earlier use that as
我们之前讨论过的使用
a completion proposal and then hit go so
完成建议，然后点击继续
let's try that again
让我们再试一次
all right directory look at that we get
好的目录看看我们得到
auto completion for these different
自动完成这些不同的
records that's because I didn't type
记录是因为我没有输入
anything and if I type in just BR for
任何东西，如果我只输入BR
example I get two suggestions Brian do
例如，我有两个建议，布莱恩
so and Brian close out and of course I
所以，布莱恩关闭了，当然我
can hit tab hit go and it says I'm
可以按跳动去，它说我
working with Brian close L so there we
和Brian一起工​​作L，所以我们
go now we've we've got a we've looked at
现在走，我们已经看到了
just a few of the ways to to use the
只是几种使用
spring shell project to sort of build an
spring shell项目来构建一个
application now there's a little bit of
应用程序现在有一点
polish here this the rest of the stuff
在这里擦亮其余的东西
it we're gonna talk about here isn't
我们要谈论的不是
strictly speaking a spring shell
严格来说是Spring Shell
specific but it's stuff that you might
具体的，但这是你可能会做的
care about when you're building a shell
关心何时构建外壳
based application first of all consider
基于应用程序首先考虑
that we have logging right as I start
在我开始时，我们已经正确记录了日志
the application up all of this stuff
应用程序把所有这些东西
sort of muddies the experience and if
有点使经验混乱，如果
you don't care that I don't care but if
你不在乎我不在乎，但是如果
you do care it's easy enough to fix that
您确实很容易解决该问题
right you
对你
go to your build and stay logging and I
去建立并保持记录，我
will download eagles off right so I'm
会马上下载老鹰，所以我
try that all right
试试吧
much better right so now we can say
好多了，现在我们可以说
connect Eagles username J password P
连接Eagles用户名J密码P
connected and such a very clean now I
连接，现在很干净
happen to be a big fan of this ask
碰巧是这个要求的忠实粉丝
anybody who knows me knows that this is
任何认识我的人都知道这是
I you know I rank this among the a fine
我知道我在罚款中排名
art masterpieces of the world that said
说的世界艺术杰作
maybe you're of the inclination that you
也许你很喜欢你
want to change it and that's ok you know
要更改它，没关系，您知道
that's ok I've I've I've gotten no
可以，我可以，我可以
reason why you shouldn't do that so
为什么你不应该这样做
we're gonna change the basket the the
我们要把篮子换成
ASCII art the banner artwork here
ASCII艺术这里的横幅艺术品
ok so I'm gonna copy a pre-written
好，我要复制一个预先写好的
banner txt to my downloads shellcode
横幅txt到我的下载shellcode
source main resources banner dot txt all
来源主要资源横幅点txt全部
right
对
and I guess that's it actually we can
我想实际上就是这样
just rebuild it not bad huh
只是重建它还不错吧
spring crm spring tip slide there's a
spring crm spring tip slide有一个
Twitter handle ok not bad so we still
Twitter的处理还可以，所以我们还是
are we still have to run java - jar do
我们仍然需要运行java-jar吗
you notice that I have to enjoy - jar
你注意到我必须享受-jar
target blah blah blah and that's because
目标等等等等，那是因为
it's it's just a jar it's a fat jar that
这只是一个罐子这是一个胖罐子
you know has all everything it needs
你知道所有需要的东西
inside of it except for the JDK but it's
除了JDK之外，它的内部是
still you need to you need to you need
仍然你需要你需要你需要
to tell the D decay to run right so we
告诉D衰减正确运行，所以我们
can take it one step further and
可以更进一步
customize the build itself so here we're
自定义构建本身，所以在这里
gonna go to the build plug in the spring
会在 Spring 去做插件
boot maven plugin and make this an
启动Maven插件并使之成为
executive jar and what's gonna happen is
行政罐子，将要发生的是
I'll I'll be able to run the jar without
我可以不用
having to use the Java CLI or Java
必须使用Java CLI或Java
command and it's still gonna be there
命令，它仍然会在那里
it's don't need it eventually but you
最终不需要它，但是你
know I don't have to worry about it too
知道我也不必担心
much so there is not bad huh not bad so
好多了，还不错吧，还不错，所以
we have a user name
我们有一个用户名
password P good we can make a directory
密码P好，我们可以建立一个目录
search with one of these records good we
用这些记录之一搜索很好，我们
can disconnect and we can quit all right
可以断开连接，我们可以退出
so my friend with that we've looked at
所以我和那个朋友一起看过
the spring shell project we looked at
我们看过的Spring Shell项目
how to build a simple spring shell based
如何建立一个简单的基于Spring 的外壳
application it's worth understanding
应用程序值得理解
that anything you can do in spring you
Spring 你可以做的一切
know and then print out you can do with
知道然后打印出来就可以
spring shell so you can have this
Spring Shell，所以你可以有这个
connected to a WebSocket based chat for
连接到基于WebSocket的聊天
example you could use this to talk to a
例如，您可以使用它与
REST API using a spring web flex web
使用Spring Web Flex Web的REST API
client or a rest template or ever
客户或休息模板或曾经
talking to back back-end services you
与后端后端服务交谈
could have this driving the creation of
可能会带动
jobs you know spring batch jobs or
您知道Spring Batch作业或
sending messages into channels or or
发送消息到频道或
doing whatever you want right it's just
做任何你想做的事
all it's just a nice easy to use easy to
所有这只是一个很好的易于使用的易于
script easy to automate easy to interact
脚本易于自动化，易于交互
with tool and it's lightweight it
工具轻巧
doesn't take a lot of doesn't take a lot
不需要很多，不需要很多
of resources to talk about this jar to
谈论这个罐子的资源
move it around so we we have a serum
移动它，所以我们有血清
shell here it's 12 MiG's that whole jar
这是整个罐子里的12米格
all the functionality in the jar
罐子里的所有功能
everything is - talking about jar so
一切都是-谈论罐子，所以
we've got that we didn't get to look at
我们得到了我们没有去看
a number of other features I mean
我的意思是其他一些功能
there's just obviously can imagine
显然可以想象
there's a lot of other features beyond
除此以外，还有很多其他功能
this you can make certain parameters to
这可以使某些参数
your to your commands optional for
您的命令可选
example and more to the point there's
例子，更重要的是
even support for Jake commander which is
甚至支持杰克指挥官
a separate project that was created by
由创建的一个单独的项目
cedric voiced is it I think the the
塞德里克说的是
gentleman behind testing G for example
例如测试G的绅士
he created a project for binding
他创建了一个用于绑定的项目
arguments on the command line
命令行中的参数
it's called Jake commander they're very
被称为杰克指挥官，他们非常
useful you can use that with spring
有用，可以在Spring 上使用
shell if you want and that allows you to
外壳，如果您想要的话，那么您可以
bind parameters to a command to a POJO
将参数绑定到命令到POJO
as opposed to having to declare custom
而不是必须声明习俗
parameters or rather yeah parameters for
参数或更确切地说是
each command method here and you know
每个命令方法在这里，你知道
there's many many other things besides
除此以外，还有很多其他的事情
right now it's early days yet this is
现在是早期，但这是
still the second milestone so if you
仍然是第二个里程碑，所以如果你
have feedback
有反馈
I'm sure the spring shell team and
我敢肯定Spring Shell团队和
ultimately the larger spring cloud
最终更大的 Spring Cloud
dataflow and and all the projects based
数据流以及所有基于项目的项目
on spring shell all those projects would
在春季，所有这些项目都会
appreciate any and all feedback right so
感谢所有反馈，以便如此
give it a try
试试看
let us know and with that thanks for
让我们知道，谢谢
watching and see you next time
看着下次见
you
您